{
  "players": [
    {"name":"The Murder","dicePool":0,"condition":"HEALTHY","playSheets":[{"specification":{"name":"Zph","description":"You aren't one thing, one body, you are many. A group of tiny, bodies of many types and uses, controlled by one group intelligence. You. Your many bodies might have different purposes, designs, even origins. They might die, you might need new ones, but one thing had remained true for all those eons. You are still you.","flavorText":{"text":"Consciousness is drifting now. Tiny parts in each body. Changing with the joinings, and dyings, and births of me. Now hive, now swarm, now spawn.","attribution":"Zph navigator, psychogogic manipulative capture","uuid":"e1fbe540-2212-4f66-b197-cf155c35d311"},"choices":[{"options":[{"text":"The death of a world"},{"text":"An interplanetary war"},{"text":"Bodies dying until who you were changed"},{"text":"Half your bodies parting ways"},{"text":"The zph you come from"},{"text":"Your first time in orbit"},{"text":"The first alien you met"},{"text":"Your first love"},{"text":"You, other zph mingling ‘til you were one"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose one you want to remember from your long life","answers":1},{"question":"Choose one you want to forget from your long life","answers":1}]},{"options":[{"text":"Make useful formations"},{"text":"Make humanoid forms"},{"text":"Make soft noises"},{"text":"Mostly furred or smooth"},{"text":"Mostly hived or loose"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose two to describe your many bodies","answers":2}]}],"actions":[{"description":"Let some of your bodies die of illness or old age","diceOffset":1},{"description":"Idly recall a distant memory","diceOffset":1},{"description":"Let your bodies scurry off, mound together, shift","diceOffset":1},{"description":"Do something else emerging from a long lived swarm intelligence","diceOffset":0},{"description":"Use one of your many long memories to solve a problem","diceOffset":-1},{"description":"Sacrifice some of your bodies to solve an immediate threat, no matter that you forget something when they die","diceOffset":-1},{"description":"Extend your bodies further afield to spy on something new","diceOffset":-1},{"description":"Let roughly half your bodies wander off to make a new zph","diceOffset":-4}],"uuid":"eb81a1f7-c623-4021-bf7f-1328e28e6854"},"choices":[{"specification":{"options":[{"text":"The death of a world"},{"text":"An interplanetary war"},{"text":"Bodies dying until who you were changed"},{"text":"Half your bodies parting ways"},{"text":"The zph you come from"},{"text":"Your first time in orbit"},{"text":"The first alien you met"},{"text":"Your first love"},{"text":"You, other zph mingling ‘til you were one"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose one you want to remember from your long life","answers":1},{"question":"Choose one you want to forget from your long life","answers":1}]},"answeredQuestions":[{"question":{"question":"Choose one you want to remember from your long life","answers":1},"answers":[{"text":"The zph you come from"}]},{"question":{"question":"Choose one you want to forget from your long life","answers":1},"answers":[{"text":"Bodies dying until who you were changed"}]}]},{"specification":{"options":[{"text":"Make useful formations"},{"text":"Make humanoid forms"},{"text":"Make soft noises"},{"text":"Mostly furred or smooth"},{"text":"Mostly hived or loose"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose two to describe your many bodies","answers":2}]},"answeredQuestions":[{"question":{"question":"Choose two to describe your many bodies","answers":2},"answers":[{"text":"Make humanoid forms"},{"text":"Make soft noises"}]}]}]},{"specification":{"name":"The Abductee","description":"One day a spaceship showed up on your uncontacted, backwater world and carried you away. Maybe you were in danger. Maybe there was a misunderstanding. Maybe it was a kidnapping. It's an old story. Abduction, for whatever reason.","flavorText":{"text":"I was contemplating The Broken God, and his ways, when the spaceship arrived. Black and glistening with void menace over me. I was afraid.","attribution":"Nnedi ban'Xi, as quoted by Freetravelers, a Subversive Folk","uuid":"2dc27870-97cb-459c-9bae-70026171dcf2"},"choices":[{"options":[{"text":"Your name or your family's name"},{"text":"A language no one else speaks"},{"text":"A bit of tech no one else understands"},{"text":"A bunch of pop culture references"},{"text":"A pet"},{"text":"A sense of alienation"},{"text":"Your world's location"},{"text":"A little analogue song player"},{"text":"A hobby everyone else thinks is weird"},{"text":"A single piece of preserved food for a special occurrence"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose one you still carry with you from your homeworld ","answers":1},{"question":"Choose one that was taken from you","answers":1}]}],"actions":[{"description":"Annoy people with references they don't understand","diceOffset":1},{"description":"Ask about ways to return home when it isn't the right time","diceOffset":1},{"description":"Declare that despite everything, you are superior","diceOffset":1},{"description":"Do something normal in the place where you were taken from","diceOffset":0},{"description":"Hatch a crazy plan using something low-tech from your world","diceOffset":-1},{"description":"Know how to do something simple when space tech breaks","diceOffset":-1},{"description":"Find information that might help lead you home eventually","diceOffset":-4},{"description":"Stop looking for your lost homeworld","diceOffset":-5}],"uuid":"e20641e9-9668-4ca0-891b-fdbded6b273b"},"choices":[{"specification":{"options":[{"text":"Your name or your family's name"},{"text":"A language no one else speaks"},{"text":"A bit of tech no one else understands"},{"text":"A bunch of pop culture references"},{"text":"A pet"},{"text":"A sense of alienation"},{"text":"Your world's location"},{"text":"A little analogue song player"},{"text":"A hobby everyone else thinks is weird"},{"text":"A single piece of preserved food for a special occurrence"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose one you still carry with you from your homeworld ","answers":1},{"question":"Choose one that was taken from you","answers":1}]},"answeredQuestions":[{"question":{"question":"Choose one you still carry with you from your homeworld ","answers":1},"answers":[{"text":"A bit of tech no one else understands"}]},{"question":{"question":"Choose one that was taken from you","answers":1},"answers":[{"text":"Your world's location"}]}]}]},{"specification":{"name":"Orbital Voidworker","description":"Superstitions abound about those that brave the out. Shipbreakers, hull patchers, spacing survivors. Not wise to look so long at void, dark things there, they say. Some fear you, others think you lucky, ethertouched.","flavorText":{"text":"Drink vacuum, never fear the gods. Albatross, albatross, albatross again.","attribution":"The Shipyard Worker's Song, traditional","uuid":"bbcdb845-2e54-44dd-892e-11c5456f6b06"},"choices":[{"options":[{"text":"Null-G repair, work"},{"text":"Ship boarding, combat"},{"text":"EVA survival, invention"},{"text":"Something else"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose one practical skill you bring with you","answers":1}]},{"options":[{"text":"Light and shadow bends near you"},{"text":"Orbits and ether are quiet near you"},{"text":"Sound deadens to silence near you"},{"text":"Some say Deep Wild Dark itself watches you"},{"text":"Some say dark deities lure you towards destiny"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose one odd skill you bring with you","answers":1}]}],"actions":[{"description":"Have a dark god, void monster, or other etheric entity attack you","diceOffset":5},{"description":"Have your luck fail you at the worst possible times","diceOffset":2},{"description":"Feel claustrophobic inside stations and ships","diceOffset":1},{"description":"Unnerve more normal people","diceOffset":1},{"description":"Look peculiar, behave oddly, or do something else absentminded","diceOffset":0},{"description":"Move through space easily","diceOffset":-1},{"description":"Accidentally intimidate someone with how you look","diceOffset":-1},{"description":"Accidentally have someone superstitious or fearful help you","diceOffset":-1},{"description":"Use your practical skill above to solve an vacuum problem","diceOffset":-1},{"description":"Use your more odd skill above to solve a small problem","diceOffset":-1},{"description":"Have luck help in a pinch","diceOffset":-1},{"description":"Do something in ether no one else on the crew can do","diceOffset":-2},{"description":"Invoke the dark, the out","diceOffset":-3},{"description":"Go into the black, embrace whatever happens","diceOffset":-6}],"uuid":"4672b4a3-0a39-4a54-a385-0939300f690a"},"choices":[{"specification":{"options":[{"text":"Null-G repair, work"},{"text":"Ship boarding, combat"},{"text":"EVA survival, invention"},{"text":"Something else"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose one practical skill you bring with you","answers":1}]},"answeredQuestions":[{"question":{"question":"Choose one practical skill you bring with you","answers":1},"answers":[{"text":"Null-G repair, work"}]}]},{"specification":{"options":[{"text":"Light and shadow bends near you"},{"text":"Orbits and ether are quiet near you"},{"text":"Sound deadens to silence near you"},{"text":"Some say Deep Wild Dark itself watches you"},{"text":"Some say dark deities lure you towards destiny"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose one odd skill you bring with you","answers":1}]},"answeredQuestions":[{"question":{"question":"Choose one odd skill you bring with you","answers":1},"answers":[{"text":"Light and shadow bends near you"}]}]}]}],"items":[]},
    {"name":"PLAGUE","dicePool":0,"condition":"HEALTHY","playSheets":[{"specification":{"name":"Angel","description":"Something from outside wrote you into this universe's skin alone, without instruction. As a being of pure energy you are indestructible. But to interact with everything else, to have an identity, most angels, including you, have commissioned carved bodies for themselves. Fragile and fallible bodies that now shelter and identify you.","flavorText":{"text":"Lo brethren! We are cast out in this universe of dark! Rise up! Rise together for the glory of all angelkind! Be the light to pierce creation!","attribution":"Her Angelic Highness","uuid":"flavor_c874850d-b339-4566-8a4c-ab1f70058eb0"},"choices":[{"options":[{"text":"Made of clay, stone","uuid":"option_662faefe-5df8-4124-af6f-ace074832e4b"},{"text":"Made of metal, plastic","uuid":"option_e15b57c0-e24c-4a01-ae31-f1224f24862b"},{"text":"Made of glass, crystal","uuid":"option_36f1058c-6e37-4c31-ab41-84f3baa5d06a"},{"text":"Looks common","uuid":"option_f2cda81c-d635-4e54-87f7-702f86dd5a85"},{"text":"Looks almost alive","uuid":"option_7a05b985-bb26-436c-bc15-6f0da24c0ef4"},{"text":"It has multiple wings","uuid":"option_3f58c095-f807-46b7-988b-5a3498014b73"},{"text":"Is unique in creation","uuid":"option_1ba881a0-0043-466b-8cab-f7e8d054d9c4"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose two qualities of your physical body","answers":2,"uuid":"questionspec_b0406386-6c48-41a8-b7a9-aa958ebb0a79"}],"uuid":"choicespec_2e40ac6e-682d-4c03-ad77-c567c3b1e0a8"},{"options":[{"text":"It's male or masculine","uuid":"option_1541448b-6b43-43cd-9ad3-80ead645f2b8"},{"text":"It's female or feminine","uuid":"option_9e767121-41a6-430d-b339-ad2e8f457ac9"},{"text":"It will age and decay","uuid":"option_7cc93b10-fd02-4ddb-ad1d-e2b2363504ce"},{"text":"It's bound to one location","uuid":"option_60165060-3788-4ba6-8861-a14b117456c7"},{"text":"It's mind can be wrong","uuid":"option_30c73a9d-7be9-43f2-990c-3987aa0a32e5"},{"text":"It cannot do some physical actions","uuid":"option_52cbb611-66f5-47a8-bae5-fb8f91849e39"},{"text":"It's cracked, warped or marked by time","uuid":"option_335f4176-94df-4838-b8aa-9c6141b454cc"},{"text":"It's not perfectly beautiful like you were","uuid":"option_745ce903-fce8-42bc-89fe-05ff3378eb8e"},{"text":"You have altered it, but your body resists change","uuid":"option_8c57821b-a192-4d5b-8c03-a79a6d9926c0"},{"text":"Other people judge it","uuid":"option_b368a259-2c50-4151-a176-1c95da723f54"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose three limits imposed on you by physical your body","answers":3,"uuid":"questionspec_0d89149e-8931-4d40-8285-6dcefb08e6e7"}],"uuid":"choicespec_21268ef9-7c55-4ae6-9287-ed3851375077"}],"actions":[{"description":"Be limited by your body","diceOffset":1,"uuid":"action_ac3abc02-f321-414a-b16e-3aef40673474"},{"description":"Have your body hurt or break","diceOffset":1,"uuid":"action_174df1f8-f230-4b63-ba84-788bdb869dde"},{"description":"Mourn for when you were immortal energy","diceOffset":1,"uuid":"action_c928b5cb-9c83-443e-8718-e746dad8b1be"},{"description":"Do something else as a being written into the universe","diceOffset":0,"uuid":"action_b0df3cde-35d1-47d2-8d45-8f68e0452ec7"},{"description":"Momentarily have your energy leave your body to solve a problem","diceOffset":-1,"uuid":"action_2d7dd787-a66f-4318-8c93-77c8b7966fad"},{"description":"Move impossibly quick, be impossibly strong, defy the laws of physics, or otherwise break limits","diceOffset":-3,"uuid":"action_b1837839-3231-4b9e-8cb5-878340caf687"},{"description":"If possible, modify your body","diceOffset":-5,"uuid":"action_268a79c7-348f-4943-a2d4-9f8f105bc437"}],"uuid":"playsheetspec_1059a6f9-9657-4765-872e-8c80ce29a25e"},"choices":[{"specification":{"options":[{"text":"Made of clay, stone","uuid":"option_662faefe-5df8-4124-af6f-ace074832e4b"},{"text":"Made of metal, plastic","uuid":"option_e15b57c0-e24c-4a01-ae31-f1224f24862b"},{"text":"Made of glass, crystal","uuid":"option_36f1058c-6e37-4c31-ab41-84f3baa5d06a"},{"text":"Looks common","uuid":"option_f2cda81c-d635-4e54-87f7-702f86dd5a85"},{"text":"Looks almost alive","uuid":"option_7a05b985-bb26-436c-bc15-6f0da24c0ef4"},{"text":"It has multiple wings","uuid":"option_3f58c095-f807-46b7-988b-5a3498014b73"},{"text":"Is unique in creation","uuid":"option_1ba881a0-0043-466b-8cab-f7e8d054d9c4"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose two qualities of your physical body","answers":2,"uuid":"questionspec_b0406386-6c48-41a8-b7a9-aa958ebb0a79"}],"uuid":"choicespec_2e40ac6e-682d-4c03-ad77-c567c3b1e0a8"},"answeredQuestions":[{"question":{"question":"Choose two qualities of your physical body","answers":2,"uuid":"questionspec_b0406386-6c48-41a8-b7a9-aa958ebb0a79"},"answers":[{"text":"Looks common","uuid":"option_f2cda81c-d635-4e54-87f7-702f86dd5a85"},{"text":"Made of glass, crystal","uuid":"option_36f1058c-6e37-4c31-ab41-84f3baa5d06a"}],"uuid":"answeredquestion_579dcf55-d001-483a-a79c-fd2ba37e1698"}],"uuid":"choice_ca4cd70c-3e52-4758-b8b1-ad82a981f617"},{"specification":{"options":[{"text":"It's male or masculine","uuid":"option_1541448b-6b43-43cd-9ad3-80ead645f2b8"},{"text":"It's female or feminine","uuid":"option_9e767121-41a6-430d-b339-ad2e8f457ac9"},{"text":"It will age and decay","uuid":"option_7cc93b10-fd02-4ddb-ad1d-e2b2363504ce"},{"text":"It's bound to one location","uuid":"option_60165060-3788-4ba6-8861-a14b117456c7"},{"text":"It's mind can be wrong","uuid":"option_30c73a9d-7be9-43f2-990c-3987aa0a32e5"},{"text":"It cannot do some physical actions","uuid":"option_52cbb611-66f5-47a8-bae5-fb8f91849e39"},{"text":"It's cracked, warped or marked by time","uuid":"option_335f4176-94df-4838-b8aa-9c6141b454cc"},{"text":"It's not perfectly beautiful like you were","uuid":"option_745ce903-fce8-42bc-89fe-05ff3378eb8e"},{"text":"You have altered it, but your body resists change","uuid":"option_8c57821b-a192-4d5b-8c03-a79a6d9926c0"},{"text":"Other people judge it","uuid":"option_b368a259-2c50-4151-a176-1c95da723f54"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose three limits imposed on you by physical your body","answers":3,"uuid":"questionspec_0d89149e-8931-4d40-8285-6dcefb08e6e7"}],"uuid":"choicespec_21268ef9-7c55-4ae6-9287-ed3851375077"},"answeredQuestions":[{"question":{"question":"Choose three limits imposed on you by physical your body","answers":3,"uuid":"questionspec_0d89149e-8931-4d40-8285-6dcefb08e6e7"},"answers":[{"text":"It's female or feminine","uuid":"option_9e767121-41a6-430d-b339-ad2e8f457ac9"},{"text":"It's male or masculine","uuid":"option_1541448b-6b43-43cd-9ad3-80ead645f2b8"},{"text":"Other people judge it","uuid":"option_b368a259-2c50-4151-a176-1c95da723f54"}],"uuid":"answeredquestion_b5fac909-e7eb-4695-86ca-82e53014a5d0"}],"uuid":"choice_f7270817-5822-49c8-86e6-5acabb2a91eb"}],"uuid":"playsheet_8d9f3ab8-70ba-4594-b24b-a39df671bbf5"},{"specification":{"name":"The Prophesied","description":"A product of the chosen one industry, born to greatness, specifically bred for one thing, circumstances of creation and youth all controlled to produce an end product. Yet here you are Freetraveling. Not doing that. Why?","flavorText":{"text":"“Welcome to Winnipeg! Leading the way in the chosen one industry with our patented corp oracles! If you're here, it's because we foretold it.","attribution":"Planetary Winnipeg slogan, prior to the Constabulary ousting SaintsCo","uuid":"flavor_d3789817-c3e5-4b32-8b4b-f96a589d9ce3"},"choices":[{"options":[{"text":"Conquer or free a world","uuid":"option_86712714-4175-4712-bcc1-0451bdca88ed"},{"text":"Kill or serve a king","uuid":"option_da188d27-381c-4803-a83d-21a811901374"},{"text":"Die or live for someone","uuid":"option_e5457814-fb26-4a8a-a51f-c7d2ace42256"},{"text":"Burn everything down","uuid":"option_7e753398-0568-44ed-9a08-d55708710c2d"},{"text":"Preserve memory","uuid":"option_9480523a-09a9-4098-9a29-a643d9ab7e6e"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose what you were meant to do","answers":1,"uuid":"questionspec_f8b70809-dfe5-4e29-8fa7-109e9d2f5eb6"}],"uuid":"choicespec_942305c8-c1f1-40b3-b3f2-c08c4dad0f08"},{"options":[{"text":"Brutal training","uuid":"option_c37a1fee-a81e-4525-94b7-86b64a8e870d"},{"text":"Mass sacrifice","uuid":"option_b713f5d3-bfcf-40b8-929d-191797087f74"},{"text":"Unholy magic","uuid":"option_fe59d752-7a3f-4a61-af1d-5547322af2cd"},{"text":"Prophecy manipulation","uuid":"option_579a6bc2-bab8-42ba-b418-3b7827a3e494"},{"text":"Bloodline bullshit","uuid":"option_2632f0ee-2c01-4388-8ed4-f3bf46cd67f9"},{"text":"Mad science","uuid":"option_7ff51967-63bd-40d8-b06b-ef5cc5bb3432"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose what horror was done to make you","answers":1,"uuid":"questionspec_3e670e74-ff96-4a2e-bd5b-01e71c2cda8c"}],"uuid":"choicespec_492f0820-6508-47e9-b1ea-dfb2a78b6681"}],"actions":[{"description":"Hide why you left, why you can't be what you were born to be","diceOffset":1,"uuid":"action_2f9bc1b9-cfa9-42b2-a902-7e5d22b18b95"},{"description":"Feel pressure to do something, achieve greatness, save the day","diceOffset":1,"uuid":"action_664e9489-2014-4fd9-a458-4095a4ba878b"},{"description":"Push yourself into a situation that does not need you to be there","diceOffset":1,"uuid":"action_4a743cba-c29c-4a4e-851a-71216d6c330b"},{"description":"Have flashbacks, fear you aren't doing what you were meant to","diceOffset":1,"uuid":"action_d106ff82-005a-4f6d-9089-d9b294c1908a"},{"description":"Do something neither embracing nor rejecting to your supposed great, glorious destiny","diceOffset":0,"uuid":"action_26b3beab-f1bd-4c58-a2bd-cf7c62788928"},{"description":"Be vulnerable, and with that vulnerability have someone else help you","diceOffset":-1,"uuid":"action_6fc6273c-7502-4a1a-b4d9-95fbe5e90ea1"},{"description":"Use a thing they forced you to do to actually solve a problem","diceOffset":-1,"uuid":"action_5082796a-b3d6-4a91-a594-af72389c8adc"},{"description":"Have someone help you because they believe your supposed destiny","diceOffset":-3,"uuid":"action_db57d0dc-e6e8-45d7-bf0b-430673ad0916"},{"description":"Intimidate someone into helping you because of what you are","diceOffset":-3,"uuid":"action_a680973f-23ee-47f1-95c3-015792355718"},{"description":"Break prophecy, reject the past, explain why you left","diceOffset":5,"uuid":"action_5a16d86b-ee95-4c30-a5d8-be13a318a371"}],"uuid":"playsheetspec_828d6595-ab7a-4dc6-92a9-85aa7da07a30"},"choices":[{"specification":{"options":[{"text":"Conquer or free a world","uuid":"option_86712714-4175-4712-bcc1-0451bdca88ed"},{"text":"Kill or serve a king","uuid":"option_da188d27-381c-4803-a83d-21a811901374"},{"text":"Die or live for someone","uuid":"option_e5457814-fb26-4a8a-a51f-c7d2ace42256"},{"text":"Burn everything down","uuid":"option_7e753398-0568-44ed-9a08-d55708710c2d"},{"text":"Preserve memory","uuid":"option_9480523a-09a9-4098-9a29-a643d9ab7e6e"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose what you were meant to do","answers":1,"uuid":"questionspec_f8b70809-dfe5-4e29-8fa7-109e9d2f5eb6"}],"uuid":"choicespec_942305c8-c1f1-40b3-b3f2-c08c4dad0f08"},"answeredQuestions":[{"question":{"question":"Choose what you were meant to do","answers":1,"uuid":"questionspec_f8b70809-dfe5-4e29-8fa7-109e9d2f5eb6"},"answers":[{"text":"Burn everything down","uuid":"option_7e753398-0568-44ed-9a08-d55708710c2d"}],"uuid":"answeredquestion_26235b96-9324-4e11-9818-b43d3d3dc9ae"}],"uuid":"choice_2488c40d-9319-4e33-bfab-9e190f896ae3"},{"specification":{"options":[{"text":"Brutal training","uuid":"option_c37a1fee-a81e-4525-94b7-86b64a8e870d"},{"text":"Mass sacrifice","uuid":"option_b713f5d3-bfcf-40b8-929d-191797087f74"},{"text":"Unholy magic","uuid":"option_fe59d752-7a3f-4a61-af1d-5547322af2cd"},{"text":"Prophecy manipulation","uuid":"option_579a6bc2-bab8-42ba-b418-3b7827a3e494"},{"text":"Bloodline bullshit","uuid":"option_2632f0ee-2c01-4388-8ed4-f3bf46cd67f9"},{"text":"Mad science","uuid":"option_7ff51967-63bd-40d8-b06b-ef5cc5bb3432"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose what horror was done to make you","answers":1,"uuid":"questionspec_3e670e74-ff96-4a2e-bd5b-01e71c2cda8c"}],"uuid":"choicespec_492f0820-6508-47e9-b1ea-dfb2a78b6681"},"answeredQuestions":[{"question":{"question":"Choose what horror was done to make you","answers":1,"uuid":"questionspec_3e670e74-ff96-4a2e-bd5b-01e71c2cda8c"},"answers":[{"text":"Mad science","uuid":"option_7ff51967-63bd-40d8-b06b-ef5cc5bb3432"}],"uuid":"answeredquestion_8eef73a7-4043-49f9-b0c6-3f549287695e"}],"uuid":"choice_53d00d2b-a3a1-4136-a5cd-4a848028606f"}],"uuid":"playsheet_ce9dc6b1-5ce6-408a-8bc1-661dd08ffd63"},{"specification":{"name":"Astral Gardener","description":"We're all systems. Emergent computer networks, emergent biospheres, ecosystems, biotech, biology, bodies. From the personal all the way to the planetary. You tend those gardens.","flavorText":{"text":"Bodies contain ecosystems, which are contained in ships, such. Ecosystems. Which move in capitalism, kingdoms, cults, dimensions. Ecosystems.","attribution":"Rogue terraforming z-machine found floating in Deep Wild Dark","uuid":"flavor_a357f51d-97a4-48e4-9575-453e3bc4682b"},"choices":[{"options":[{"text":"Microbiology","uuid":"option_acdd396f-d934-4531-9e29-bd3dc7f06f43"},{"text":"Personal biology","uuid":"option_b4fc8ce0-bef6-4db9-8052-4374bcd79b9e"},{"text":"Planetary Ecosystems","uuid":"option_4a2b42f8-1340-4b41-b96f-abc53955d2ab"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose a scale of biology you operate on","answers":1,"uuid":"questionspec_56c176df-7167-4af4-b706-74bae11853ec"}],"uuid":"choicespec_02aade36-904b-490a-b474-789544167c2c"},{"options":[{"text":"Healed injuries","uuid":"option_7493ec25-0b3c-4247-9c21-65a7f1bc1ea1"},{"text":"Cancerous growth","uuid":"option_69971e93-93f9-4680-95d9-e23614b7ec66"},{"text":"Accelerated processes","uuid":"option_0ca25cd7-ca22-4c82-b797-545ce162d8de"},{"text":"Blighted biology","uuid":"option_615f85a6-19ed-479c-898c-4539de5bc910"},{"text":"Shifted homeostasis","uuid":"option_728b032a-01ae-4813-9c44-10cd247d7cd1"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose one stem line","answers":1,"uuid":"questionspec_77bda622-e500-4a91-8c84-1c0eb5984268"}],"uuid":"choicespec_13fd1b9f-7493-4b76-87ae-1b8a365e3188"}],"actions":[{"description":"Be unable to deal with something artificial, or technological","diceOffset":1,"uuid":"action_abc6b5c1-9107-4e18-8e17-b80a5c4c23a6"},{"description":"Scare someone when you interact with and change biology","diceOffset":1,"uuid":"action_d02ba955-1f31-4888-8677-76c9485b2dc9"},{"description":"Look over your tools, syringes, knives, vials, and instruments","diceOffset":1,"uuid":"action_8f5417eb-983f-4b55-8728-b7f131bba1e6"},{"description":"Admire an emergent system","diceOffset":1,"uuid":"action_0e831486-1996-4cdc-b1a0-998b927d50a0"},{"description":"Study something organic, or do something disgusting, you can write it down if you want","diceOffset":0,"uuid":"action_bbfeaeca-32f3-44ce-873f-41503349f24b"},{"description":"Solve a small problem with an organic thing","diceOffset":-1,"uuid":"action_1bd1d20f-9126-49b3-8c69-8985de3c4990"},{"description":"Using something on your scale of biology preemptively warn of danger from an organic thing","diceOffset":-1,"uuid":"action_6618776e-0126-490d-b760-f8227f0add2b"},{"description":"Using something from on scale of biology supply a need","diceOffset":-1,"uuid":"action_dcc1bc78-e995-43d2-923d-4d5a631b002f"},{"description":"Using a tool, take away your stem line from an organic thing","diceOffset":-2,"uuid":"action_432b3475-ac79-4f62-a552-dea8dba03958"},{"description":"Using a tool, add your stem line to an organic thing","diceOffset":-2,"uuid":"action_801fc239-cec0-45a9-b08c-8e9601efc6f3"},{"description":"Using something you have previously studied, make new tools and say what they do","diceOffset":-2,"uuid":"action_8e5f51b5-f788-45d2-aa24-6cfc00bb76af"},{"description":"If you have new tools, change the scale of biology you operate on","diceOffset":-4,"uuid":"action_022e7adb-c856-483b-9757-d49bdf28a3cd"},{"description":"If you have new tools, change the way you interact with biology","diceOffset":-4,"uuid":"action_e42c678e-d1f0-496b-9155-7ad9405ce33c"}],"uuid":"playsheetspec_6c5ba3d2-0cd2-468e-b8b3-0dbfda4d6198"},"choices":[{"specification":{"options":[{"text":"Microbiology","uuid":"option_acdd396f-d934-4531-9e29-bd3dc7f06f43"},{"text":"Personal biology","uuid":"option_b4fc8ce0-bef6-4db9-8052-4374bcd79b9e"},{"text":"Planetary Ecosystems","uuid":"option_4a2b42f8-1340-4b41-b96f-abc53955d2ab"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose a scale of biology you operate on","answers":1,"uuid":"questionspec_56c176df-7167-4af4-b706-74bae11853ec"}],"uuid":"choicespec_02aade36-904b-490a-b474-789544167c2c"},"answeredQuestions":[{"question":{"question":"Choose a scale of biology you operate on","answers":1,"uuid":"questionspec_56c176df-7167-4af4-b706-74bae11853ec"},"answers":[{"text":"Personal biology","uuid":"option_b4fc8ce0-bef6-4db9-8052-4374bcd79b9e"}],"uuid":"answeredquestion_206de1d3-b59b-4e5e-b65c-33936e35dbeb"}],"uuid":"choice_34140bff-28f0-47ba-a5ea-a70cb9b459d5"},{"specification":{"options":[{"text":"Healed injuries","uuid":"option_7493ec25-0b3c-4247-9c21-65a7f1bc1ea1"},{"text":"Cancerous growth","uuid":"option_69971e93-93f9-4680-95d9-e23614b7ec66"},{"text":"Accelerated processes","uuid":"option_0ca25cd7-ca22-4c82-b797-545ce162d8de"},{"text":"Blighted biology","uuid":"option_615f85a6-19ed-479c-898c-4539de5bc910"},{"text":"Shifted homeostasis","uuid":"option_728b032a-01ae-4813-9c44-10cd247d7cd1"}],"questions":[{"question":"Choose one stem line","answers":1,"uuid":"questionspec_77bda622-e500-4a91-8c84-1c0eb5984268"}],"uuid":"choicespec_13fd1b9f-7493-4b76-87ae-1b8a365e3188"},"answeredQuestions":[{"question":{"question":"Choose one stem line","answers":1,"uuid":"questionspec_77bda622-e500-4a91-8c84-1c0eb5984268"},"answers":[{"text":"Blighted biology","uuid":"option_615f85a6-19ed-479c-898c-4539de5bc910"}],"uuid":"answeredquestion_67601098-3e42-4d4e-a03f-d10a7abad389"}],"uuid":"choice_b868a2f1-8e9f-418d-9f9c-55cc73d9625d"}],"uuid":"playsheet_506d3dad-c9a2-42dd-83aa-66c53d5ccbcb"}],"items":[],"uuid":"player_f727f4d5-f1ad-42cc-b4b2-c4d10d03ba53"}
  ]
}